Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
My name is Catherine and today we have a very complicated topic for you.
我是Catherine，今天我们有一个非常复杂的话题要讲。
That's right.
没错。
This is an upper intermediate lesson, a little bit more difficult and we're talking all about
这是一节中高级课程，难度稍大，我们要讨论的是
taxes, paychecks and all the information for when you work in the United States.
在美国工作时涉及的税收、工资单以及所有相关信息。
That's right.
没错。
It confuses me and I'm American.
连我这个美国人都觉得困惑。
So take a close listen.
所以请仔细听。
We're going to listen to this dialogue one time and we'll be back in a moment to discuss
我们先听一遍这段对话，稍后回来讨论
what's going on.
具体内容。
Hey, Susan, have you got a sec?
嘿，Susan，你有空吗？
I have some questions about my paycheck.
我有些关于工资单的问题。
You bet, Emily.
当然可以，Emily。
Pull up a chair.
搬把椅子过来坐。
Well, this is my first paycheck here in the States and there are a few things I don't
嗯，这是我在美国的第一张工资单，有些地方我
understand.
不太明白。
First off, what is this FICA and SUI SDI tax and why are there deductions both from
首先，这个FICA和SUI SDI税是什么？为什么医疗保险和我的健康保险计划
Medicare and from my health insurance plan?
都要扣钱？
OK, let's start from the top of your pay stub.
好，我们从工资单的顶部开始看。
This number here represents your gross pay.
这个数字代表你的总工资。
Yes, that's easy enough to understand.
是的，这个很容易理解。
Then here we have a series of deductions.
然后这里有一系列的扣款项。
First off are the federal ones.
首先是联邦扣款。
FICA stands for Federal Insurance Contribution Act or something like that.
FICA代表联邦保险贡献法案之类的。
It's your federal income tax.
这是你的联邦所得税。
And then there's Social Security and Medicare, which are both federal programs to help you
然后是社会保障和医疗保险，这两个联邦项目是为了在你退休后
out after you retire or if you are unable to work.
或无法工作时提供帮助。
All right, I see.
好的，我明白了。
So the Medicare isn't actually a health insurance I can use now.
所以医疗保险并不是我现在能用的健康保险。
That's right.
没错。
Below the federal deductions are the state deductions.
联邦扣款下面是州扣款。
There's the state income tax.
有州所得税。
And then this SUI SDI tax you were asking about is paying into an unemployment and or
然后你问的这个SUI SDI税，是向州设立的失业
disability fund that our state has set up.
或残疾基金缴费。
But you can see that it's a pretty small quantity that they take.
但你可以看到他们扣的金额很小。
Yeah, I don't mind giving them a dollar fifty for that.
是啊，我不介意给他们一块五毛钱。
So there are two separate income taxes, one at a state level and one at a federal level.
所以有两个独立的所得税，一个是州级的，一个是联邦级的。
That's right.
没错。
Not all states have an income tax.
不是所有州都有所得税。
Some use higher property taxes or sales taxes instead.
有些州用更高的房产税或销售税来代替。
I see.
我明白了。
All right.
好的。
Well, I think everything else I can figure out on my own.
嗯，我想其他东西我自己能搞明白。
The deductions for health insurance and my 401k are pretty self-explanatory.
健康保险和401k的扣款都挺一目了然的。
Thanks for your help, Susan.
谢谢你的帮助，Susan。
No problem.
不客气。
All those deductions do add up and nobody's net pay is as high as they'd like.
所有这些扣款加起来确实不少，没人能拿到自己想要的净工资。
I can understand why you'd want some explanation.
我能理解你为什么想要解释。
Yeah, I guess it's the same in the UK.
是啊，我想在英国也一样。
I just never paid much attention.
我只是以前从没太注意过。
See you later.
回头见。
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So obviously a lot of vocab there, a lot of acronyms as well, like FICA and all that stuff.
很明显这里有很多词汇，还有很多缩写，比如FICA之类的。
We'll take a look at that in a little bit.
我们稍后会看一下。
First, let's start off with some language on Language Takeaway.
首先，我们从“语言要点”开始讲一些语言点。
Language Takeaway.
语言要点。
So when you get paid, there's a very important number you want to look at or a couple of
所以当你拿到工资时，有一个非常重要的数字你要看，或者几个
numbers.
数字。
These are called deductions.
这些叫做扣款。
Now, why do deductions make people sad, Marco?
那么，Marco，为什么扣款让人不开心呢？
Because a deduction is to take away or reduce.
因为扣款就是拿走或减少。
So obviously if your salary is, let's say, $1,000 and you have $500 deductions, then
所以很明显，如果你的工资是，比如说，1000美元，而你有500美元的扣款，那么
you only get five instead of 1,000.
你只能拿到500而不是1000。
All right.
好的。
So deductions mean what money is being taken away from you.
所以扣款指的是从你那里拿走的钱。
All right.
好的。
So that's money that's deducted for certain taxes or certain programs.
这些钱是为了某些税收或某些项目而扣除的。
It's important to remember that deduct, to deduct, is the opposite of to add.
记住很重要，deduct（扣除）是add（增加）的反义词。
It means to take away.
意思是拿走。
To take away, that's right.
拿走，没错。
So Emily had some questions about her salary and so she brought her pay stub to Susan to
所以Emily对她的工资有些疑问，于是她拿着工资单去找Susan
ask her, why are all these deductions?
问，为什么有这么多扣款？
Why am I not getting all my salary?
为什么我拿不到全部工资？
That's right.
没错。
So pay stubs are very important pieces of paper.
所以工资单是非常重要的文件。
Basically when you go to a store and you buy something, you get a receipt.
基本上，你去商店买东西时，会拿到收据。
Well when you go to work and you get paid, you get a receipt for your payment.
而你去工作拿到工资时，你会得到一张付款收据。
That means that it shows you how much money you earn and all of these deductions.
这意味着它显示你赚了多少钱以及所有这些扣款。
So if you're paid every month, you get a pay stub every month.
所以如果你每月领工资，你每月都会收到一张工资单。
If you're paid every two weeks, you get a pay stub every two weeks.
如果你每两周发一次工资，那你每两周就会收到一张工资单。
Okay.
好的。
So it's basically a little receipt that tells you you have been paid and how much you were
所以它基本上是一张小收据，告诉你已经发了工资以及发了多少。
paid.
发了多少。
That's right.
没错。
All right.
好的。
So Susan started explaining about her gross salary and her net salary.
所以苏珊开始解释她的总工资和净工资。
All right.
好的。
And these are the two most important numbers on your pay stub.
而这两个数字是你工资单上最重要的两个数字。
On your pay stub it will say gross pay.
在你的工资单上会写着总工资。
Not gross like icky gross, but like total.
不是那种恶心的“gross”，而是指总额。
So in total you earn $1,000 a month, but that's not how much money you have in your bank because
所以你一个月总共赚1000美元，但这并不是你银行里的钱，因为
the money that you earn is actually a little bit different because of these deductions
你赚的钱实际上有点不同，因为还有我们提到的这些扣除项。
we mentioned.
我们提到的这些扣除项。
So the net pay is the actual amount of money you get to keep.
所以净工资是你实际能留下的钱。
Right.
对。
So the company will pay $1,000, but with taxes and all these deductions, the actual money
所以公司会支付1000美元，但扣掉税和所有这些扣除项后，你实际拿到的钱
that you get is less and that's called the net pay.
更少，这就叫净工资。
So it's important when you're looking at these numbers, look at your gross pay.
所以当你查看这些数字时，重要的是要看你的总工资。
Is that correct?
对吗？
And then afterwards, look at your net pay.
然后之后，再看你的净工资。
Is that what money you actually received?
那是你实际收到的钱吗？
That's right.
没错。
All right.
好的。
So now getting into a little bit of taxes and the type of taxes that we have out there.
现在我们来谈谈税收以及我们现有的各种税种。
Not considering the taxes for the salary, this is a different one.
不是指工资税，这是另一种税。
We have a property tax.
我们有房产税。
That's right.
没错。
So some places in America tax you on the amount of money you earn at your job, but a lot of
所以美国有些地方会根据你工作赚的钱来征税，但很多地方
others like to collect taxes from different areas.
喜欢从不同领域收税。
So property tax is one of those.
房产税就是其中之一。
If you own land, if you own a house or a condo, you will pay a property tax every year.
如果你拥有土地、房子或公寓，你每年都要交房产税。
Every year you have to pay for owning this property.
每年你都要为拥有这处房产而交税。
That's right.
没错。
So basically you're paying the state for the land that you have or the space that you have.
所以基本上你是在为你拥有的土地或空间向州政府交钱。
And the bigger your house is, the bigger the land is, the more money you pay.
你的房子越大，土地越大，你交的钱就越多。
And you have to pay the same value every year or does it change over time?
你每年都要交同样的金额，还是它会随时间变化？
It can change over time.
它会随时间变化。
You hear this sometimes, property taxes are, or property value increases and so then property
你有时会听到，房产税会随着房产价值上涨而上涨，所以房产税
tax will probably increase as well.
可能也会增加。
Okay.
好的。
And what about sales tax?
那销售税呢？
I think this is very straightforward, but how does it work?
我觉得这个很简单，但它具体是怎么运作的？
Well, it's straightforward, Marco, but I don't think they have this in many other places
嗯，马可，它很简单，但我觉得世界上很多其他地方
in the world.
没有这个税。
China, for example, we don't really have a sales tax, so people don't have to worry about
比如中国，我们实际上没有销售税，所以人们不用操心
it.
这个。
But a sales tax is a small tax that you pay every time you buy something.
但销售税是你每次买东西时交的一小笔税。
Right.
对。
All right.
好的。
If I buy a TV and the TV is $100, it's possible that the sales tax is 3%.
如果我买一台电视，电视是100美元，销售税可能是3%。
I pay $103.
我付103美元。
So that's another way that you are taxed, not on how much money you make, but on the
所以这是另一种征税方式，不是根据你赚多少钱，而是根据
purchases that you make.
你的消费。
That makes sense.
有道理。
I can buy a lot of cool things, cars, TVs.
我可以买很多酷东西，车、电视。
I'm paying more money to my state to provide services like schools and roads and things
我付更多的钱给州政府，用来提供像学校、道路之类的服务。
like that.
诸如此类。
Okay.
好的。
So a lot of interesting things here.
这里有很多有趣的东西。
I think we can move on now to specifically talking about the taxes related to people's
我想我们现在可以继续，专门谈谈与人们工资相关的税，或者在美国它是怎么运作的。
salaries or how it works in the United States.
记住，我们这里专门讨论的是美国的情况。
Remember that we are talking specifically about the United States here.
So let's take a look at that now on Fluency Builder.
现在我们来看看Fluency Builder上的内容。
Fluency Builder.
Fluency Builder。
All right.
好的。
So one of the scary acronyms here, Marco, was FICA.
马可，这里有一个吓人的缩写词，叫FICA。
The FICA.
FICA。
It looks very strange here.
它看起来很奇怪。
What is this FICA?
这个FICA是什么？
Well, this is an acronym.
嗯，这是一个缩写词。
And remember, acronyms are words that stand for other words.
记住，缩写词是代表其他词的词。
So F, federal, I, insurance, C, contribution, and A, act.
所以F代表联邦，I代表保险，C代表贡献，A代表法案。
So federal insurance contribution act.
所以是联邦保险贡献法案。
Basically, this is a federal tax.
基本上，这是一种联邦税。
That means that it's everyone in the country.
这意味着全国每个人都要交。
Everyone has to pay it, no matter where you live.
无论你住在哪里，每个人都要交。
Yeah.
是的。
Illinois, New York, California, everyone has to pay.
伊利诺伊州、纽约州、加利福尼亚州，每个人都要交。
And how much is this tax?
这个税是多少？
Do you know?
你知道吗？
I do not know.
我不知道。
It's called a graduated income tax.
这叫做累进所得税。
That means that people who earn very little pay very little.
意思是收入很低的人缴很少的税。
People who earn a lot pay more.
收入高的人缴更多的税。
Okay.
好的。
So this is something that everyone has to pay and that's why it's called federal tax,
所以这是每个人都必须缴纳的东西，这就是为什么它被称为联邦税，
right?
对吧？
That's right.
没错。
So federal means national and state means more local for your own state.
所以联邦指的是国家层面，而州指的是更地方性的、你所在的州。
Okay.
好的。
Now, she is obviously paying the federal tax that everyone has to pay.
现在，她显然在缴纳每个人都必须缴纳的联邦税。
And what about Medicare?
那医疗保险呢？
All right.
好的。
So this is not a tax per se.
所以这本身并不是一种税。
This is actually a deduction that goes into kind of a fund.
这实际上是一种扣除，进入某种基金。
You know, it's a government program.
你知道，这是一个政府项目。
And when you're older, when you're retired, you will receive benefits from the federal
当你年纪大了，退休了，你会从联邦
government, from the United States government to get healthcare.
政府，也就是美国政府那里获得福利，用于医疗保健。
So Medicare is a kind of healthcare that is paid for by the US government.
所以医疗保险是一种由美国政府支付的医疗保健。
I see.
我明白了。
So when you're older, you don't really have to pay for your hospital bills then because
所以当你年纪大了，你实际上不必支付医院账单，因为你
you worked and contributed to this Medicare fund, then you can go and get treatment.
工作过并向这个医疗保险基金缴过费，然后你就可以去接受治疗。
That's right.
没错。
Or you pay for part of it and they pay for part of it.
或者你支付一部分，他们支付一部分。
So it depends on the system.
所以这取决于系统。
But yes, it's a way to get healthcare through the government.
但没错，这是一种通过政府获得医疗保健的方式。
Okay.
好的。
And your next word is interesting because we've heard about Social Security before.
你的下一个词很有趣，因为我们以前听说过社会保障。
You have the Social Security card, which is basically your ID.
你有社会保障卡，这基本上就是你的身份证。
It states also that you are an American.
它也表明你是美国人。
But what is the Social Security fund now that you are contributing to?
但你现在在缴款的社会保障基金是什么呢？
Well, basically, this is another government program that is designed to make sure that
嗯，基本上，这是另一个政府项目，旨在确保
people are comfortable when they stop working.
人们在停止工作后生活舒适。
Because when you stop working, you don't have any income anymore.
因为当你停止工作时，你不再有任何收入。
You need money to live.
你需要钱来生活。
And so your whole life, you're paying into this fund and the government will then give
所以你一生都在向这个基金缴款，然后政府会
you the money back, some money, to basically live off of when you're retired.
把钱还给你一些，基本上让你在退休后靠它生活。
Okay.
好的。
And so how long do you actually have to work in order to be eligible for Social Security?
那么，你实际上需要工作多久才有资格享受社会保障？
I believe you have to be 65 to be eligible for Social Security, but I'm not sure.
我相信你必须65岁才有资格享受社会保障，但我不确定。
It's either 60 or 65.
要么是60岁，要么是65岁。
I'm not there yet.
我还没到那个年龄。
All right.
好的。
And actually, another one that's very similar is you have this 401K, which is actually a
实际上，另一个非常相似的是你有这个401K，这实际上是一个
very interesting name for this tax or fund.
对这种税或基金来说非常有趣的名字。
Yeah, 401K is more of an investment.
是的，401K更像是一种投资。
So a 401K is something that you put money into every month or year to access later on
所以401K是你每个月或每年存钱，以便以后
when you're retired.
退休时使用的东西。
So again, it's a kind of security for you.
所以，这又是一种对你的保障。
If you work every day, every year for 30 years, 40 years, you want to have some money when
如果你每天、每年工作30年、40年，你希望在
you're all done.
一切结束后有一些钱。
And this is basically a retirement savings plan.
这基本上是一个退休储蓄计划。
So what is the difference between Social Security and the 401K, or are they the same?
那么社会保障和401K有什么区别，还是它们是一样的？
I think the difference is where the money goes.
我认为区别在于钱去了哪里。
I'm not 100%.
我不完全确定。
But all of these are like, you have to give the government this money, or can I say, hey,
但所有这些都像是，你必须把这笔钱交给政府，或者我可以说，嘿，
I don't want to, don't worry about me.
我不想，别担心我。
I don't need Social Security.
我不需要社会保障。
I'm saving all on my own.
我自己存钱。
And can I refuse to pay these taxes?
我可以拒绝缴纳这些税吗？
401K, yes, you can refuse.
401K，是的，你可以拒绝。
It's not a tax.
它不是一种税。
It's just something that you can...
它只是你可以...
Usually this is not a government program.
通常这不是一个政府项目。
This is something that the company that you work for will set up for you.
这是你工作的公司为你设立的。
But Medicare and Social Security, these are things that you have to pay into.
但医疗保险和社会保障，这些是你必须缴款的东西。
Because even if you're rich and you have all this money, there are a lot of people in America
因为即使你很有钱，有这么多钱，美国有很多人
that don't have any of this.
什么都没有。
And so we consider it something that we do for each other as much as for ourselves.
所以我们认为这是我们为彼此做的，也是为自己做的。
Because also, Medicare and Medicaid, these are programs that you can also be eligible
因为还有，医疗保险和医疗补助，这些项目你即使25岁或30岁
for even if you're 25 years old or 30 years old.
也可能有资格享受。
You're poor, you don't have a job.
你穷，没有工作。
So these are social programs.
所以这些是社会项目。
Okay, very good.
好的，非常好。
It's very, very interesting.
非常非常有趣。
You see that, obviously, this is why in movies, you see that people make fun of taxes and
你看，显然，这就是为什么在电影里，你会看到人们拿税开玩笑，
how much tax in America there is and how you can't escape taxes.
以及美国有多少税，你如何逃不掉税。
But it's interesting to see how it's made up and why you are giving your money to the
但看看它是如何构成的，以及为什么你要把钱交给
government.
政府，这很有趣。
That's right.
没错。
So let's listen to today's dialogue again.
那我们再来听一遍今天的对话吧。
It was pretty complicated.
它挺复杂的。
So hopefully you've understood a little bit more after we've talked about it now.
希望在我们讨论过后，你现在能多理解一些。
Hey, Susan, have you got a sec?
嘿，苏珊，你有空吗？
I have some questions about my paycheck.
我关于工资单有些问题。
You bet, Emily.
当然有，艾米丽。
Pull up a chair.
拉把椅子坐下吧。
Well, this is my first paycheck here in the States.
嗯，这是我在美国的第一张工资单。
And there are a few things I don't understand.
有些地方我不太明白。
First off, what is this FICA and SUI SDI tax?
首先，这个FICA和SUI SDI税是什么？
And why are there deductions both from Medicare and from my health insurance plan?
为什么医疗保险和我的健康保险计划都要扣钱？
Okay, let's start from the top of your pay stub.
好，我们从工资单的顶部开始看。
This number here represents your gross pay.
这个数字代表你的总工资。
Yes, that's easy enough to understand.
是的，这个很容易理解。
Then here we have a series of deductions.
然后这里有一系列的扣款。
First off are the federal ones.
首先是联邦的扣款。
FICA stands for Federal Insurance Contribution Act or something like that.
FICA代表联邦保险缴款法案之类的。
It's your federal income tax.
这是你的联邦所得税。
And then there's Social Security and Medicare, which are both federal programs to help you
然后是社会保障和医疗保险，这两个都是联邦项目，在你退休后或无法工作时
out after you retire or if you are unable to work.
帮助你。
All right, I see.
好的，我明白了。
So the Medicare isn't actually a health insurance I can use now.
所以医疗保险并不是我现在能用的健康保险。
That's right.
没错。
Below the federal deductions are the state deductions.
联邦扣款下面是州扣款。
There's the state income tax.
有州所得税。
And then this SUI SDI tax you were asking about is paying into an unemployment and or
然后你问的这个SUI SDI税，是缴纳到我们州设立的失业和
disability fund that our state has set up.
或残疾基金里的。
But you can see that it's a pretty small quantity that they take.
但你可以看到他们扣的金额很小。
Yeah, I don't mind giving them a dollar fifty for that.
是啊，我不介意给他们一块五毛钱。
So there are two separate income taxes, one at a state level and one at a federal level.
所以有两种独立的所得税，一种是州级的，一种是联邦级的。
That's right.
没错。
Not all states have an income tax.
不是所有州都有所得税。
Some use higher property taxes or sales taxes instead.
有些州用更高的财产税或销售税来代替。
I see.
我明白了。
All right.
好的。
Well, I think everything else I can figure out on my own.
嗯，我想其他东西我自己能搞明白。
The deductions for health insurance and my 401k are pretty self-explanatory.
健康保险和我的401k退休计划的扣款都挺一目了然的。
Thanks for your help, Susan.
谢谢你的帮助，苏珊。
No problem.
不客气。
All those deductions do add up and nobody's net pay is as high as they'd like.
所有这些扣款加起来确实不少，没人拿到手的工资能像他们期望的那么多。
I can understand why you'd want some explanation.
我能理解你为什么想要解释一下。
Yeah, I guess it's the same in the UK.
是啊，我想在英国也是一样的。
I just never paid much attention.
我以前只是没太注意。
See you later.
回头见。
All right.
好的。
So another interesting thought that came up was, well, where does the money for government
所以另一个有趣的想法是，政府支出的钱
spending come from?
从哪里来？
So because you have all these taxes that are for you, basically you have property tax or
因为你有所有这些为你而设的税，基本上你有财产税，
maybe does it come from sales tax that maybe the government can make roads and parks and
或者可能来自销售税，这样政府才能修路、建公园
stuff like this?
之类的东西？
Well, that's the thing.
嗯，这就是关键。
Remember earlier we talked about federal and state taxes.
记得我们之前谈过联邦税和州税。
Well, if it's a state tax like sales tax, in America I can pay sales tax in California,
如果是州税，比如销售税，在美国我在加州要付销售税，
but maybe in New Mexico there is no sales tax.
但也许在新墨西哥州就没有销售税。
So this is a state tax.
所以这是州税。
And that means that the state government can use the money for state projects, parks, roads,
这意味着州政府可以用这些钱来搞州项目、公园、道路
things like that.
之类的东西。
But then the Federal Insurance Contribution Act, the FICA, this federal tax, that is something
但联邦保险缴款法案，也就是FICA，这个联邦税，是用来
that's used for our military, our government.
支持我们的军队和政府的。
This pays the paychecks of people in Congress, the president.
这用来支付国会成员和总统的工资。
This is where all the money to pay them comes from.
所有付给他们的钱都来自这里。
And so basically the state taxes pay for state benefits and programs and the federal taxes
所以基本上，州税用于州福利和项目，而联邦税
pay for these nationwide programs.
用于全国性的项目。
So that's, I think one of the most interesting things about this topic is that the United
所以我认为这个话题最有趣的一点是，美国
States is like 50 small countries that kind of have their own little governments.
就像50个小国家，各自有自己的一套小政府。
They have their own taxes and they have their own rules.
它们有自己的税收和规则。
Like in some states you can start driving when you're 16 and others when you're 15.
比如在一些州，你16岁就能开车，而在其他州是15岁。
And so it's like all these little small countries, but at the same time you have this one mega
所以就像所有这些小国家，但同时你又有这一个超级
country that has federal taxes and federal insurance and military and all this.
大国，有联邦税、联邦保险和军队等等。
That's true.
确实如此。
And you know, it's an interesting fact about American history that the most conflict in
而且你知道吗，美国历史上一个有趣的事实是，我们国家
our country has really come down to these two groups.
最大的冲突实际上都归结于这两个群体。
One group believes that the federal government, so that's the national government, should
一个群体认为联邦政府，也就是国家政府，应该
have more power than the states.
比州拥有更多权力。
And another group believes that the state should have more power.
另一个群体认为州应该拥有更多权力。
And that is a big problem.
这是一个大问题。
You know, this disagreement that we've had in America that goes back to 1776 and the
你知道，我们在美国一直存在的这种分歧，可以追溯到1776年和
founding fathers.
开国元勋们。
And so I don't think it's something that is fixed.
所以我认为这不是一个已经解决的问题。
You know, these things change, you know, sometimes more federal power, sometimes less, but it's
你知道，这些事情会变，有时联邦权力大些，有时小些，但这
a very interesting part of American history.
是美国历史中非常有趣的一部分。
And also it would be interesting to hear from our users how it works over there, because
而且，听听我们的用户在其他地方的情况也会很有意思，因为
I know that approximately a rough estimate is that around 30 to 40% of Americans' income
我知道，粗略估计大约有30%到40%的美国人的收入
goes to tax, right?
都用来交税了，对吧？
About that, yeah.
差不多吧，嗯。
So almost half of your money goes into taxes.
所以几乎你一半的钱都进了税收。
So I wonder how much it is in other people's countries.
所以我想知道在其他国家是多少。
Maybe they have 60% of taxes or maybe 10.
也许他们有60%的税，或者10%。
Yeah.
嗯。
So let us know.
所以告诉我们吧。
Our website is EnglishPod.com.
我们的网站是EnglishPod.com。
We hope to see you guys there.
我们希望能在那儿见到你们。
All right.
好的。
Bye.
再见。